const objVocQuestions = {
    basico     : {
        classroom : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : 'Pizarra',
                answer   : "whiteboard"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : 'Alumno',
                answer   : "student"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : 'Silla',
                answer   : "chair"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : 'Mesa',
                answer   : "table"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : 'Libro',
                answer   : "book"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : 'Dibujar',
                answer   : "draw"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : 'Mapa',
                answer   : "map"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : 'Papel',
                answer   : "paper"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : 'Cortar',
                answer   : "cut"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : 'Cuaderno',
                answer   : "notebook"
            },
            {
                num      : 11,
                question : 'Pegamento',
                answer   : "glue"
            },
            {
                num      : 12,
                question : 'Maestra',
                answer   : "teacher"
            },
            {
                num      : 13,
                question : 'Bolígrafo',
                answer   : "pen"
            },
            {
                num      : 14,
                question : 'Escribir',
                answer   : "write"
            },
            {
                num      : 15,
                question : 'Colores',
                answer   : "colors"
            },
            {
                num      : 16,
                question : 'Estuche',
                answer   : "case"
            },
            {
                num      : 17,
                question : 'Tijeras',
                answer   : "scissors"
            },
            {
                num      : 18,
                question : 'Goma',
                answer   : "rubber"
            },
            {
                num      : 19,
                question : 'Marcadores',
                answer   : "markers"
            },
            {
                num      : 20,
                question : 'Regla',
                answer   : "ruler"
            },
        ],
        bedroom   : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : 'Cama',
                answer   : "bed"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : 'Almohada',
                answer   : "pillow"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : 'Osito de peluche',
                answer   : "teddy bear"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : 'Pelota',
                answer   : "ball"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : 'Armario',
                answer   : "closet"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : 'Muñeca',
                answer   : "doll"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : 'Moqueta',
                answer   : "carpet"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : 'Reloj',
                answer   : "clock"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : 'Mesita de noche',
                answer   : "night table"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : 'Juguete',
                answer   : "toy"
            },
            {
                num      : 11,
                question : 'Cuna',
                answer   : "cradle"
            },
            {
                num      : 12,
                question : 'Cuento de Hadas',
                answer   : "fairy tale"
            },
            {
                num      : 13,
                question : 'Sueño',
                answer   : "dream"
            },
            {
                num      : 14,
                question : 'Manta',
                answer   : "blanket"
            },
            {
                num      : 15,
                question : 'Zapatillas de Casa',
                answer   : "slippers"
            },
            {
                num      : 16,
                question : 'Ventana',
                answer   : "window"
            },
            {
                num      : 17,
                question : 'Persiana',
                answer   : "blind"
            },
            {
                num      : 18,
                question : 'Escritorio',
                answer   : "desk"
            },
            {
                num      : 19,
                question : 'Ordenador',
                answer   : "computer"
            },
            {
                num      : 20,
                question : 'Ordenador Portátil',
                answer   : "laptop"
            },
        ],
        myfamily  : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : 'Antepasado',
                answer   : "ancestor"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : 'Abuelo',
                answer   : "grandfather"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : 'Abuela',
                answer   : "grandmother"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : 'Mamá',
                answer   : "mom"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : 'Papá',
                answer   : "father"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : 'Gemelos',
                answer   : "twins"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : 'Primo',
                answer   : "cousin"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : 'Tío',
                answer   : "uncle"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : 'Tía',
                answer   : "aunt"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : 'Sobrino',
                answer   : "nephew"
            },
            {
                num      : 11,
                question : 'Sobrina',
                answer   : "niece"
            },
            {
                num      : 12,
                question : 'Hermano',
                answer   : "brother"
            },
            {
                num      : 13,
                question : 'Hermana',
                answer   : "sister"
            },
            {
                num      : 14,
                question : 'Cuñado',
                answer   : "brother in law"
            },
            {
                num      : 15,
                question : 'Cuñada',
                answer   : "sister in law"
            },
            {
                num      : 16,
                question : 'Marido',
                answer   : "husband"
            },
            {
                num      : 17,
                question : 'Esposa',
                answer   : "wife"
            },
            {
                num      : 18,
                question : 'Familiares',
                answer   : "relatives"
            },
            {
                num      : 19,
                question : 'Novio',
                answer   : "boyfriend"
            },
            {
                num      : 20,
                question : 'Novia',
                answer   : "girlfriend"
            },
        ]
    },

    intermedio : {
        classroom : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : 'A board whith a smooth, white surface, often attached to a wall.',
                answer   : "whiteboard"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : 'A person who is learning at a college or university.',
                answer   : "student"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : 'Long, thin object, often made of wood, for writing or drawing.',
                answer   : "pencil"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : 'A long, flat piece of plastic, used for measuring or drawing straight lines.',
                answer   : "ruler"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : 'Device used for cutting materials such as paper, made of two sharp blades.',
                answer   : "scissors"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : 'A special pen often used for underlining text.',
                answer   : "marker"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : 'Small piece of rubber used to remove marks made by a pencil.',
                answer   : "eraser"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : 'Small piece of rubber used to remove marks made by a pencil.',
                answer   : "eraser"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : 'A book of plain paper or paper with lines, for writing on.',
                answer   : "notebook"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : 'To make marks that represent letters, words, or numbers on a surface.',
                answer   : "write"
            },
            {
                num      : 11,
                question : 'Someone whose job is to teach in a school or college.',
                answer   : "teacher"
            },
        ],
        bedroom   : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : "A cover for a window that is pulled up or down by a string.",
                answer   : "blind"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : "A flat surface, usually supported by four legs, used for putting things on.",
                answer   : "table"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : "A small bed for a baby, specially one that moves side to side.",
                answer   : "cradle"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : "A small table that is kept at the side of a bed.",
                answer   : "beside table"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : "A traditional story written for children.",
                answer   : "fairy tale"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : "A rectangular cloth bag filled with soft material, used for resting in bed.",
                answer   : "pillow"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : "A flat cover made of wool or similiar material, used on a bed.",
                answer   : "blanket"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : "A type of table that you can work at, often one with drawers.",
                answer   : "desk"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : "Small room with a door, used for storing things, like clothes.",
                answer   : "closet"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : "A child's toy in the shape of a small person or baby.",
                answer   : "doll"
            },
        ],
        myfamily  : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : "My mother's son is my:",
                answer   : "brother"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : "My father's sister is my:",
                answer   : "aunt"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : "My aunt's son is my:",
                answer   : "cousin"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : "My aunt's husband is my:",
                answer   : "uncle"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : "My mother's father is my:",
                answer   : "grandfather"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : "My father's mother is my:",
                answer   : "grandmother"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : "My sister's husband is my:",
                answer   : "brother in law"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : "My brother's wife is my:",
                answer   : "sister in law"
            },
        ]
    },

    avanzado   : {
        classroom : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : 'A dark surface on the wall that teachers write on with chalk.',
                answer   : "blackboard"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : 'Work that teachers give their students to do at home.',
                answer   : "homework"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : 'The time between the lessons.',
                answer   : "break"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : 'The room where the students and a teacher are.',
                answer   : "classroom"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : 'The person who looks after the school.',
                answer   : "caretaker"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : 'A formal written, spoken or practical test.',
                answer   : "exam"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : 'The people who work at a school.',
                answer   : "staff"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : 'An area of knowledge that is studied in school, college, or university.',
                answer   : "subject"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : 'A mechanical, small handheld device for making a sharp point on pencils.',
                answer   : "pencil sharpener"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : 'A large bag used to carry things on your back, often used by students.',
                answer   : "backpack"
            },
        ],
        bedroom   : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : 'A clock that you can set to wake up at a particular time with a loud noise.',
                answer   : "alarm clock"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : 'A piece of forniture with drawers in wich you keep things such as clothes.',
                answer   : "chest of drawers"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : 'A big bed enough for two people to sleep in.',
                answer   : "double bed"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : 'A large, soft, flat bag filled with feathers used as a covering on bed.',
                answer   : "duvet"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : 'Device for giving light, especially one that has a covering or is contained within something.',
                answer   : "lamp"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : 'A tall cupboard in which you hang your clothes.',
                answer   : "wardrobe"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : 'A device shaped like a box with a screen that displays images.',
                answer   : "television"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : 'A large piece of thin cloth used on a bed for sleeping on or under.',
                answer   : "sheet"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : 'A cloth cover for a pillow that can easily be removed and washed.',
                answer   : "pillowcase"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : 'A place in the wall where electrical devices can be attached to electricity.',
                answer   : "outlet"
            },
        ],
        myfamily  : [
            {
                num      : 1,
                question : 'Your ___ is your male parent.',
                answer   : "father"
            },
            {
                num      : 2,
                question : 'Your ___ is the woman who gave birth to you.',
                answer   : "mother"
            },
            {
                num      : 3,
                question : 'Your ___ is the child of your uncle or aunt.',
                answer   : "cousin"
            },
            {
                num      : 4,
                question : 'Some people refer to their grandmother as ___.',
                answer   : "granny"
            },
            {
                num      : 5,
                question : "Someone's ___ is the woman they are married to.",
                answer   : "wife"
            },
            {
                num      : 6,
                question : "Your ___ are your brothers or sisters",
                answer   : "siblings"
            },
            {
                num      : 7,
                question : "Your ___ are the members of your family.",
                answer   : "relatives"
            },
            {
                num      : 8,
                question : "A ___ is two people who are married or living together.",
                answer   : "couple"
            },
            {
                num      : 9,
                question : "The son of my father's brother is my ___.",
                answer   : "cousin"
            },
            {
                num      : 10,
                question : "A person who looks after a child not his or her own is a ___.",
                answer   : "foster parent"
            },
        ]
    },

};